const chatbotData = [
    {
        question: "Hello",
        answer: "Hi! How can I assist you with Menzenic products today?",
    },
    {
        question: "Hi",
        answer: "Hello! How can I assist you with Menzenic products today?",
    },
    {
        question: "What is Menzenic?",
        answer: "Menzenic is a brand that offers a range of high-quality intimate hygiene products.",
    },
    {
        question: "I want to buy something",
        answer: "which kind of product you want to buy",
    },
    {
        question: "What products does Menzenic offer?",
        answer: "Menzenic offers a variety of intimate hygiene products, including intimate washes, wipes, and menstrual cups.",
    },
    {
        question: "Are Menzenic products safe to use?",
        answer: "Yes, Menzenic products are made with safe and gentle ingredients specifically designed for intimate use.",
    },
    {
        question: "Where can I purchase Menzenic products?",
        answer: "You can purchase Menzenic products on our official website or through authorized retailers.",
    },
    {
        question: "Are Menzenic products eco-friendly?",
        answer: "Yes, Menzenic is committed to sustainability and offers eco-friendly options, such as biodegradable wipes and reusable menstrual cups.",
    },
    {
        question: "How often should I use Menzenic intimate wash?",
        answer: "Menzenic intimate wash can be used daily during your regular bathing routine for optimal freshness and hygiene.",
    },
    {
        question: "Can I use Menzenic products during my menstrual cycle?",
        answer: "Yes, Menzenic products are suitable for use during your menstrual cycle. Our menstrual cups provide a comfortable and eco-friendly alternative to traditional menstrual products.",
    },
    {
        question: "Are Menzenic products suitable for sensitive skin?",
        answer: "Yes, Menzenic products are formulated to be gentle and suitable for sensitive skin. However, it's always recommended to perform a patch test before use if you have known allergies or sensitivities.",
    },
];

export default chatbotData;
